I found myself lost and alone on this journey
Though my heart wandered far and wide, I could move not an inch
But now I can depart for any distant land
Now that we've met on this road
Even the unfamiliar songs of travelers
Can spark nostalgia in me when I'm with you
If the world we dreamed of exists somewhere,
Then let's go search for it beyond the wind
Through chilling dawns,
Through arid noons,
Through shivering nights,
Let's go see what lies at the end
Um...
This is our final co-conspirator.
I'm Martin Liebert of Lemerio Trading.
I'm N-Norah Arendt.
Let's not waste any time.
After all, business is like fresh fish in a kitchen.
If we aren't quick about things, everything will go to waste.
Will everything go according to plan?
If we fail, there won't be a future ahead of us.
Wolf and a Pack of Pups
You must be kidding.
The sun hasn't even set.
Well, that's because...
I'm going ahead of you. Catch up as soon as you can.
S-Sir!
It's okay. He's just ignorant about shepherds and how dangerous the roads can be at night.
He's shouldering the very future of Lemerio Trading.
It's to be expected.
The stars are really pretty.
They look all right.
They're far prettier in my homeland.
Who'd have thought we'd be able to talk about something so trivial under these circumstances?
You won't last long if you're always uptight.
Yeah, you're right.
Tomorrow we'll arrive at that forbidden passage.
It feels like just about anything could show up here.
If we encounter wolves, do not panic.
I guarantee that I'll deliver you safely to town.
May God be with us.
Hey.
Do you think we'll be safe from the wolves?
Not a chance.
We're already surrounded.
What?
Well, even if that were to happen, I could guarantee your safety.
I can't say the same about the others.
We'll be in trouble unless everyone's okay.
I truly don't know if that's possible.
The forest is in the direction of the wind.
If wolves are out there, they're sharpening their fangs in anticipation of a sheep feast.
That's a smart dog.
It's really getting on my nerves.
What do you mean by that?
That dog knows who I really am and is trying to intimidate me.
Is that so?
Good grief. He really doesn't know his place.
Do you think Norah has noticed?
If the smuggling fails, Norah will be worse off than all of us.
If we keep quiet, there's a possibility that we can escape, but...
Geez, you really are obsessed with blondes, aren't you?
I told you what kind of punishment she could get, didn't I?
There's no way a frail girl like her could bear something like that.
In that case, you should protect her with all your might.
Holo...
I hope the wolves won't show up while we're here.
Oh, yes, indeed.
We should arrive at Lamtra by noon if we leave at daybreak.
The rest will be up to me from there on out.
I'm going to prepare for tomorrow by getting some sleep.
Sleep well.
Lawrence-san, stay back.
There's no need to panic.
Wake up and stay alert.
Did you manage to drive them away?
They're no longer nearby.
The wolves around here are always like this.
They don't ever howl or show signs they're about to attack.
It just always feels like they're watching us.
True. It's strange that they don't howl.
I hope things turn out well.
As do I.
Um... Do you know a lot about wolves, Miss Holo?
Oh, it's just that you seemed to notice the wolves rather quickly last night.
You think? I somehow realized they were there, that's all.
Really?
Maybe I was simply feeling tense.
The men with us are useless, after all.
Don't you think so, too?
N-Not at all.
What do you think about this one?
Don't mind him.
Say whatever comes to mind.
You've figured him out pretty well.
Well, it's ridiculous to ask a woman who's traveling with a man
whether she knows a thing or two about wolves.
Why's that?
Come nighttime, a male wolf will always appear—
tempted by this helpless, adorable rabbit.
Surely you'll agree that a rabbit who is devoured by a wolf every night couldn't fail to know something about them!
Um... Does that mean...
What a cute reaction.
In our case, it's the opposite.
My companion is the true rabbit. If I left him on his own, he'd likely die of loneliness.
In any case, the fact that I quickly noticed the wolves was just a coincidence.
I thought you may have been a shepherd, Holo-san.
That's surprising to hear.
It's because Enek seemed very interested in you.
Oh, I bet he's fallen in love with me.
Enek has?
You think dearly of him, don't you?
He thinks he's secured your affection because of all the attention you give him.
I'm sure he's falling into selfishness and seeking the attention of others.
You should act indifferent once in a while.
That's how you handle his reins.
I'll be sure to follow your advice if he flirts with another.
That's good.
I want to indulge him as much as I can right now, though.
This will be my last job as a shepherd regardless of whether or not we're successful.
Do you still have concerns about her?
You win.
You sure got it done.
I'm so glad! I thought you might have come back empty-handed.
Is that how I looked?
Anyone holding such a large sum of money would look tense.
Sorry for losing my composure.
Let's be on our way.
A golden tomorrow awaits the four of us.
I-Is this really the same path we traveled on?
I-It seems really different.
Enek!
Sorry, but we need to hurry.
Have they arrived?
Yes, they're on top of the hill over there.
W-Will we be all right?
Yes, but we need to hurry!
Enek!
This girl knows what she's doing.
The wolves can't do anything now.
What do you mean?
Wolves won't move in a way that will allow one of their own to get injured.
They'll carefully surround their prey and wait for the best opportunity to attack.
Enek!
This formation will allow us to slay one at the very least.
We'll be able to make it at this pace because wolves will never attack alone.
In the trees.
What is it?
It's now or never!
Stay back!
I hear that humans sometimes grumble about the reckless youths of this generation.
I feel the same way about these wolves.
Are we safe now?
N-Norah-san, answer me.
I don't know, but I'll do my best.
Give me a break!
Listen.
I'm the only one who can handle this.
Stay clear of me after you tell the girl and the young man to go ahead of us.
Why change course now?
Didn't I say they weren't normal wolves?
The pack won't chase the sheep if you do as I say.
They weren't after the sheep in the first place.
Cheap bluster.
Crude pride.
Ideals that the young have always valued.
Come on. They won't move unless you tell them to.
Partners should cooperate, should they not?
We'll hold them here.
You two go ahead with the gold as planned.
But...
No, we should leave it to them.
Let's meet at the walls of Lubinheigen.
We'll all be rich by then.
Good luck.
Stay a fair distance away from me.
It might go badly if you get too close.
You understand, don't you?
Don't you dare lose.
Were you a proper male, I'd at least get a kiss for my trouble here.
Oh, that's right.
Hold on to this for me.
I'd like to resolve things peacefully,
but I don't think I can make any promises.
If I have no clothes when we go to meet the others,
I'll be cold and you'll be troubled, I should think.
I'll see you soon.
You must keep going, Norah-san.
Do you want their deaths to be in vain?
Deaths?
Excuse me.
Let's hurry so we can repay their bravery.
Is that all you had to say?
I knew all of you were just a bunch of pups
baring your teeth for no good reason.
Holo!
Lawrence-san?
Um, yes.
You were safe after all.
Liebert told us everything.
We'd been waiting at the edge of the forest just in case, and we
decided we should look for you when we heard what happened.
I see.
I was drying my clothes in the brush since they were wet from the deluge.
Lawrence-san, where's your partner?
She isn't here.
That's reassuring to hear.
I won't ask you not to take this personally.
You're betraying us?
Lemerio Trading is betraying us?
It's just insurance.
It weighed heavy on us to hear that there would be a woman with you.
We're relieved to see that's not the case.
This might sound like an excuse, but we're in the same position you are.
We have to eliminate any danger we can.
You thought I'd blackmail you?
Such a huge amount of money could cloud anyone's eyes.
Those who choose the path of business know this.
I'll give you back your companion's memento.
I regret that I'm not able to say we'll meet again,
and it's depressing to think what's going to happen later.
Hey!
Don't you feel the same way?
Isn't she the girl he picked to do the job?
You can't mean...
Look what you did.
You shouldn't have moved.
Why don't we tie the girl up like this poor bastard?
The wolves will finish them off.
You fool! She uses pagan witchcraft, you know.
She'll manage to survive even if you blindfold her and tie her hands.
And if that happens, it'll be the end of us.
It doesn't feel right to have to kill a girl like that.
Stop bringing it up!
Sorry.
Should we finish him off?
What, you wanna do it?
No, the less blood on our hands, the better.
I agree.
Let's go. Liebert-san will be upset if we don't hurry.
His female partner is probably dead by now.
Next Episode: "Wolf and a New Journey."